export const DB = [
    {
        question:
            'a public statement that is made without giving proof, accusing somebody of doing something that is wrong or illegal',
        answer: 'allegation',
    },
    {
        question:
            'the machines and electronic parts in a computer or other electronic system',
        answer: 'hardware',
    },
    {
        question: 'the country where a person was born',
        answer: 'homeland',
    },
    {
        question: 'a baby or very young child',
        answer: 'infant',
    },
    {
        question:
            'person or company from whom you rent a room, a house, an office, etc.',
        answer: 'landlord',
    },
    {
        question: 'the great size or importance of something',
        answer: 'magnitude',
    },
    {
        question: 'the act of cutting and gathering crops',
        answer: 'harvest',
    },
    {
        question:
            'a rude way to refer to somebody who you think is very stupid',
        answer: 'idiot',
    },
    {
        question: 'the activities that are done in order to plan, organize and run a business, school or other institution',
        answer: 'administration',
    },
    {
        question:
            'a building where large quantities of goods are stored, especially before they are sent to shops to be sold',
        answer: 'warehouse',
    },
    {
        question:
            'a statement in which you say that something is less extreme than it really is',
        answer: 'understatement',
    },
    {
        question:
            'a condition in which the blood contains too many proteins, resulting in anemia',
        answer: 'macroglobulinemia',
    },
    {
        question:
            'a woman or girl who someone is having a romantic relationship with',
        answer: 'girlfriend',
    },
    {
        question:
            'a criminal organization that began in Sicily and is active in Italy and the US',
        answer: 'mafia',
    },
    {
        question:
            'an African wild animal that looks like a horse, with black or brown and white lines on its body',
        answer: 'zebra',
    },
    {
        question:
            'a drug used to reduce pain, high temperature and inflammation',
        answer: 'aspirin',
    },

];